DJURO ALFIREVIC

Belgrade, Serbia djalfirevic@gmail.com +381 64 1 84 74 84

Summary

Senior iOS Engineer with over 14 years in iOS development. Background includes iOS, macOS, .NET, Java, PHP, React and React Native development working in an Agile work environment. Complete iOS portfolio: <u>link</u>. Personal website: <u>link</u>.

Key Skills

Languages/technologies/frameworks: Objective-C, Swift, React, React Native, Java, .NET, C#, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Agile, Scrum, Git

Work Experience

Reddit: iOS Lead @ Profiles

October 2020 -

- Working as an iOS Lead

Lolly: Director of Engineering / iOS Lead

October 2019 - October 2020

- Worked as a Director of Engineering
- Worked as an iOS Lead

Symphony: Senior Software Engineer

October 2017 - June 2019

- Designed and developed iOS/macOS/React/React Native applications
- Worked as a Tech Lead and Expert Interviewer

Cubes: Senior Software Engineer / CTO

September 2015 - September 2017

- Worked as an iOS Lead
- Worked as a Software Engineering Manager/Project Manager/CTO

Ministry of Defense: Senior Software Engineer September 2006 - August 2015

- Worked on full software development lifecycle (.NET, Java)
- Worked as a Chief Software Architect
- Worked as a Software Engineering Manager

Education

Masters Degree 2001 - 2006

Military Academy, MSc Software Engineering